Guide to the Lee Family Papers, 1754-1836
Department of Special Collections
- ORIGINAL LETTERS AND DOCUMENTS
  - WADE (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - 6. 1800, Jan. 6.Manchester Sq. Emelia Wade to Lt. Col. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. asks favor for a friend, Brook Watson.
    - 7. 1800, Jan. 7.London. Emelia Wade to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.N.S. corrects previous letter.
    - 8-9. [1800], Jan. 28.N.P. Emelia Wade to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. and cover. asks another favor.
    - 10. 1800, Mar. 12.London. Emelia Wade to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. to visit Hartwell, brother in Madras.
    - 11. N.D., July 28.King St. Emelia Wade to Lt. Col. Lee. [London]. A.N.S. request.
    - 12. N.D.King St. Emelia Wade to Lt. Col. Lee. N.P. A.N.S.
  - MISCELLANEOUS (ILLEGIBLE, UNKNOWN, UNSIGNED, FRAGMENTS,ETC.) (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - 1. N.D.N.P. Illegible to [Wm.] Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Boyle, pistols.
    - 2. 1792, Aug. 22.Fendwick St. Unsigned to unknown. N.P. A.L. Bernard out of town, business for Mr. Lee, right and title to succeed.
    - 3. [1800].[Rockingham]. Small Arms to Command Lt. Col. Lee. List s. J. Rimington.
    - 4. [1800].[Rockingham]. Small Arms. Unsigned list similar to #3.
    - 5. [1800], Oct.[Rockingham] Captain's Steward and Peter Lawless. Copy of statements re: shipboard occurances and difficulties, certified and s. Wm. Lee.
    - 6. [1800, Nov.].[Rockingham]. Captain's Steward, M.H. Kelso, S.F. Robertson. Copies of statements re: shipboard difficulties, certified and s. Wm. Lee.
    - 7. N.D., June 20.Newcastle. Unknown to [Wm.] Lee. N.P. Frag. of letter. Letter from Gen. Harcourt, St. Leger's wish to exchange with Lord Paget, Gen. H. opposed, question of promotions and command, copy of unknown author's letter to Gen. Harcourt, copy of Brownrigg's letter.
    - 8. N.D.N.P. Unknown to [Wm.] Lee. N.P. Frag. of letter. Baron de Vinch, money from Lee's father, Lee's way of life at Maidstone, Lee will soon be eldest Coronet, women, libertinism, reverend punch bowl, songs, Nevil, Munro Howell, author's way of life, horses, hounds.
    - 9. 1800.Envelope with note. Colonel Sir. Wm. Lee. 1800. Papers relating to a dispute between Captain Butler of the E.I. Ship Rockingham and his passengers...
    - 10. N.D.N.P. Penny Wise and Pound Foolish handwritten verse or song or proverb.
    - 11. N.D.N.P. Handwritten note Lt. Col. Sir. Will. Lee 5 Bar+, ob. 1801 (Baronet only for two years).
    - 12. N.D.N.P. Handwritten note Wm. Lee of Hartwell in the Co. of Bucks Esqr. and Henry Harcourt of Penley in the Co. of Herts Esqr.
LEE FAMILY PAPERS - INDEXES TO REGISTER
CONTENTS
Index
Index of Dates
INDEX
[Abercromby, Sir Ralph, 1734-1801, Br. General] 1-1-1
mentioned: 1-6-7; 6-40-32
Adams, m. 5-35-14
Affleck, Sir Edmund, 1735-1788, Rear Admiral m. 6-42-35
Affleck, Sir James, 1759-1833, Lt. General, Col. 16th Dragoons 1-2(folder of 65 items); 1-3-57 (copy)
mentioned: 1-4-31; 1-6-7; 1-7-32; 2-8-25, 38; 2-14-12; 2-17-7, 8a, 8b; 3-20-23; 3-20-30; 3-22-16, 17; 4-26-35; 4-27-38; 4-31-3; 5-33-17; 5-39-40, 52, 64, 66
Aitken, William, ship's master, Snow Jason 1-1-2
Albemarle, [George Keppel, 3rd earl of, 1724-1772, General] m. 3-19-26
Aldridge, J. 1-1-3
Allingham, m. 2-13-19
Almack's Club, London m. 5-32-12
[Alwort], James, servant 1-1-4
America m.1-5-6; 3-19-18; 5-35-18
Amelia, Princess [1783-1810, daughter of George III] m. 3-19-29
Amherst, Jeffrey [1st Baron Amherst of Holmsdale, 1717-1797?] Gen. Fld. Marshal 1-1-5
Anderson, George, soldier 4-29-3
Anderson, John, Major of Brigade 1-1-6
Andrews, William, attorney? 1-1-7,8
Anson, George, officer 16th Lt. Dragoons and later Jamaica m. 1-1-11; 2-15-3; 3-23-18; 4-26-34; 4-31-40; 5-39-3
Anson, Thomas, brother of George 1-1-(9-11)
Anson family m. 3-23-13; 4-26-19, 30
Anstruther, Robert, 1768-1809, General 1-1-12
Antoine, Princess m. 1-1-33
Antonie, William Lee, cousin or nephew and ward of Sir Wm. Lee III of Hartwell 1-1-13
mentioned: 2-9-9; 4-26-1, 10, 59.
SEE ALSO: Lee, Wm. III; Fiott, John
Apeldorn, (city in the Netherlands [Apeldoorn] m. 1-3-46
Applewhaite, Thomas, Harrow schoolmate of W.L. IV 1-1-145 15
Archer, Clement, officer, 16th Lt. Dragoons 1-1-(16-25); 3-22-34.
[Mentioned: 1-2-12, 29, 62; 1-5-18; 1-6-7; 4-28-4, 50; 5-37-13; 5-39-7, 26.?]
Archer, Mary 1-1-26
Archer, William, officer 16th Lt. Dragoons 1-1-(27-31)
[Mentioned: 1-2-12, 29, 62; 1-5-18; 1-6-7; 4-28-4, 50; 5-37-13; 5-39-7, 26.?]
Armstrong, Major, Leeds Dist. 1-1-32
[Artois], Charles Philippe, comte d', 1757-1836 (later Charles Xof France) m. 4-27-37
Ascot plain m. 5-39-53
Ascot races m. 3-18-37
Ashley, C. 1-1-(33-35)
Ashford Common m. 5-39-51
Austrians m. 2-9-22; 3-23-19
Aylesbury, (town in England) m. 3-19-2; 3-23-20; 4-26-45, 59
Aylesbury, postmaster of 1-1-36
Ayllott, William (listed - Aylett) Lt. Col., 15th Lt. Dragoons 1-1-37
Badcock, Thomas Stanhope 1-3-1,2
Bagshot Club m. 6-42-36
Baker, Mrs., actress m. 2-17-14
Baker, Ben, Capt. H.P. m. 1-3-3
Balcher, John 1-3-4
Bamford, J., doctor? 1-3-5
Bancroft, m. 1-1-7
Banks, D., Lt. 1-3-6
Barber, Thomas 1-3-7,8
[Barère de Vieuzac, Bertrand, 1755-1841, Fr. lawyer, revolutionist] m. 3-23-9
Barne, Michael, Major [7th Light Dragoons] 1-3-9
Barnet, [or Chipping Barnet, England] m. 5-39-21
Barnett, W., jeweler? 1-3-(10-14)
Barrell, clerk 4-31-7
Bartlett, Mrs. m. 4-27-31, 32
Bartlett, Edmond S. 1-3-15
Barton, horse dealer? m. 5-37-44
Bateman, Greg 1-3-16,17.
Mentioned: 5-34-3
Bayley, Creole m. 3-19-16
Beauchamp, Mark, groom? 1-4-(1-8)
Beaver, J., soldier 1-3-19
Beckwith, Ferdinand, aide-de-camp, Dep. Q.M. General 1-3-(20-22)
Bedford, Francis Russell, 5th Duke of, 1765-1802 m. 2-13-41; 3-19-18; 3-25-2; 6-40-5
Bedfordshire, shrievalty of m. 2-13-30; 3-25-1, 2
Bell, B., friend 1-3-23
Bengal, India m. 3-20-10
Bennett, W., friend 1-3-24
Benton, d. 1795 m. 2-13-36
Berger, Francois, Strasbourg 1-3-25
Berg-Up-Zoon, retreat to [Berg-op-Zoom, Netherlands] m. 5-39-31
Bernard, Lady [Esther Smyth-Gookin, d. 1780] m. 4-26-65
Bernard, Mr. m. 3-24-10
Bernard, Scrope, friend, banker, agent 1-4-(9-26); 3-24-18; 4-28-38; 4-30-3, (5-9); 5-35-6.
Mentioned: 1-4-27; 4-26-59; 4-28-51, 52, 54, 55; 4-30-2; 5-34-16; 5-36-14; [6-44-2]
Bernard, Thomas, friend, Brother of Scope 1-4-(27-30).
Mentioned: 5-36-10
Betterson m. 5-39-7
Betsy (ship) m. 5-38-5
Beuvron, Duc de, SEE ALSO: Harcourt, Anne Francois m. 3-18-1
Bicknell and Co. 1-3-26
Birch, Thomas, Capt. 16th Lt. Dragoons, soldier, friend 1-4-(31-48).
Mentioned: 3-26-17
Birney, Francois, Strasbourg 1-3-27
Bishopstone SEE ALSO: Stone m. 2-14-20; 4-31-17
Blackheath, England m. 5-39-46
Blanchelard, m. 2-15-3
Blyth, [George], surgeon m. 2-8-10
Boinville, friend 1-3-(28-31)
Bokels m. 1-3-46
Bonnomet, Paris lawyer m. 5-34-33b
Boscawen, [George, 1712-1775?] General m. 3-19-26
Boston, Frederick Irby, 2nd Baron, 1749-1825 m. 2-13-33
Botany Bay, Australia m. 4-27-57; 5-34-38
Boulogne, Italy m. 5-35-18
Bourn, J. B. 1-3-(32-34)
Bourgeoisie m. 4-28-39
Boxing m. 2-15-14; 5-39-12
Boyce, William, Capt., etc., 16th Lt. Dragoons 1-4-(49-56),
Mentioned: 1-5-43; 1-6-7; 1-7-13; 5-38-2, 3; 5-39-12, 63
Boyd, Benfield & Co. 1-3-35,36
Mentioned: 3-22-31, 32
Boyle, m. 6-44-1
Bracy, M. m. 5-37-2
Bradshaw, Capt. [Lawrence?] m. 6-41-2
Bray, Thomas, farmer 1-3-(37-39)
Bread ration m. 6-42-30
Brent, agent m. 6-42-25
Bridge, apprentice & enlistee m. 1-6-14
Bridger, James, Cornet 16th Lt. Dragoons 1-3-40.
Mentioned: 1-3-60; [4-28-5 (or Bridges?)]
Bridport, Alexander Hood, Baron, later Viscount, 1726-1814, Admiral m. 4-26-39
Brighton races m. 3-18-32
Bristow, m. 5-34-34
Brock, Sir Isaac, 1769-1812, Major General m. 1-2-64
Brown, Capt. m. 1-3-53
Brown, Charles 1-3-41
Brown, Thomas, servant? 1-3-(42-45)
Brownrigg, Sir Robert, 1759-1833, General 1-3-(46-48).
Mentioned: 5-39-34; 6-44-7
Bruce, Will 1-3-49(c), 50
Brühl, Count [Heinrich von, 1700-1763] m. 2-15-10
Brulay, Caroline, Strasbourg 1-3-51
Brunswick (place), Germany m. 2-12-16
Brunswick, Princess of SEE Wales, Princess of
Bryant, John H., attorney 1-4-(57-75).
Mentioned: 3-20-11,14
Buckingham, Marquis of SEE Grenville, Geo. Nugent-Temple
Buckinghamshire Independent Club m. 6-40-16
Buckinghamshire (Bucks.) Militia m. 1-4-13, 14
Bull, m. 1-5-43
Bull, Farmer 1-3-52
Bull, William 1-3-53
Bunbury, Sir Henry Edward, 1778-1860, aide to Gen'l. Gwyn 1-3-54; 2-14-43
Burgoyne, John, 1722-1792, General m. 2-12-1
Burnap, m. 5-37-51
Burnet, John, surgeon, 16th Lt. Dragoons 1-3-(55-62).
Mentioned: 1-4-1; 2-17-8a, 8b.
Butler, Capt., shipmate E. I. Co.'s Rockingham m. 1-3-49; 1-4-22, 23; 3-18-23; 4-28-42, 46; 5-35-19; 6-44-9
Butler, John 1-3-63
Butler, Thomas Parker, officer 16th Lt. Dragoons 1-3-64, 65.
Mentioned: 2-9-19, 20; 2-12-16; 5-34-31; 5-37-29, 32
Buxton, m. 5-35-24, 25
Caesar (dog) m. 2-11-9
Calvert, Sir Harry, 1763?-1826, General [1-5-11]; 1-5-2, 3 (copies).
Mentioned: [2-9-21]; 2-11-2
Cambis, Comte de m. 2-9-9
Cambridge, England m. 1-4-10; 2-14-40; 3-25-16, 17, 19; 4-27-3
Campbell, Francis, officer 16th Lt. Dragoons 1-5-4.
Mentioned: 1-7-44
Canals m. 2-13-34
Canterbury, England m. 2-15-7; 3-18-34; 3-24-31; 5-39-9
Canterbury races m. 2-10-1, 2; 5-35-14; 5-39-9
Cantelupe, John West, Viscount (later 2nd Earl Delawarr) 1729-1777, General m. 3-19-8, 31
Cape of Good Hope m. 5-37-33
Carbonell, John, servant? 1-5-5
Carleton, m.1-3-65
Carlo, servant m.5-39-37, 39
Carmichael, Andrew, officer 16th Lt. Dragoons 1-6-(1-8).
Mentioned: 3-24-13; 4-28-59; 5-39-35
Carnegie, John, Lt. Col. 11th Lt. Dragoons m.2-9-22,27
Carnoch m.1-2-59
Carpmeal, Thomas, civil servant? 1-5-6
Carr, James, Ensign, 49th Reg't. Foot 1-5-7
Carrington, Robert Smith, 1st Baron, 1752-1838 m.4-30-5
Cartwright, Quarter Master m.1-3-15
Cater, J.A., London hatter 1-5-8, 9
Cater, Kitty, widow of J.A. 1-5-10
Cathcart, Sir William Schaw, 1st Earl, 1755-1843, soldier, diplomat 1-5-11.
Mentioned: 3-23-18; 4-26-38; 4-27-37, 60; 4-31-21; 5-37-17; 5-39-36; 6-41-4, 7
Cattle feeding m. 5-39-17
Cavalry SEE ALSO: Dragoons, specific regiments m. 1-3-64; 3-20-29; 3-22-15; 3-23-15, 19; 4-27-37; 5-38-31
Caybrook Estate m.2-13-38
Chaplin, A., Aylesbury attorney? 1-5-(12-14)
Charles, F., wife of a dragoon 1-5-15
Charlotte Sophia, Queen of England, 1744-1818 m.3-19-3, 4, 24, 25, 30; 3-23-22, 23; 3-24-8
Charsley, Robert, attorney or military legal officer 1-5-(16-18)
Chatham, John Pitt, 2nd Earl of, 1756-1835, General, etc. m.4-31-26
Chatham Barracks, near Windsor, England m. 6-42-45
Chesterfield, Philip Stanhope, 5th Earl of, 1755-1815 m.3-24-28
[Chiffney, Samuel, 1753?-1807, jockey & trainer at Newmarket] 1-5-19
Child or Childs, m.3-19-32, 33
Choiseul Regiment m.5-39-32
[Cholmeley, Montague, 1st baronet, 1772-1831 m.6-42-25
Christie, m.2-13-41
[Christie, James, 1730-1803, London auctioneer] 1-5-20, 21
Chrystie & Shaw, military agents and brokers 1-5-(22-25)
Churchill, George, Lt. Col. 15th Lt. Dragoons, General m.1-1-6; 3-20-31
Cinque Port Regiment m.2-12-7
Clark, m.6-42-36
Clayton, William, gamekeeper for Wm. Lee Antonie 1-5-26.
Mentioned: 4-28-4
Clerfayt, Charles de Croix, Count von, 1733-1798, Austrian General m.2-9-22; 4-26-41
Cleydon's Estate m.2-14-20
Coburg, Prince of SEE Saxe-Coburg. Friedrich Josias
Cockthrop, England m.3-20-15
Coffin, 1-5-27
Coldwell, Thomas 1-5-28
Coleman, Edward, veterinary 1-5-(29-34)
Mentioned: 5-33-17
Colton, Col. m.6-41-16
Collett, Wimburn & Collett 1-5-35, 36
Collyer, George Lambert, military agent, banker 1-7-1,4, 7, 10, 11, 19, (21-25), (27-31), 35, 38, 41, 43, 44; 2-8-2, (6-24), (26-28), 30, 31, 33, (41-45).
Collyer, Nathaniel, military agent, banker 1-7-(2-6), [8], 9, (12-18), [20], 21, 22, 24, 25, 27, (29-44); 2-8-1, (3-18), (20-27), 29, 31, 32, (34-45).
Collyer, Nathaniel [Jr.], soldier, son of N. and brother of G.L. m.2-8-40
Colworth, (estate) m.3-25-14
Comber, Richard, Lewes innkeeper 1-5-37
Commons, House of m.3-19-3
Commons, Speaker of the House of m.1-2-30
Compton, [Sir Herbert Abingdon Draper, 1770-1846, lawyer] 1-5-38
Compton, William, chaplain 1-5-39
Concannon, [James], officer m.5-34-6
Condé, Louis Joseph de Bourbon, Prince de, 1736-1818, French soldier m.4-28-27
Coombs, James 1-5-40
Cooper, Henry, hairdresser 1-6-9
Cooper, John, spur maker 1-6-(10-13)
Cooper, Thomas [1759-1840, natural philosopher and lawyer] 1-6-(14-16)
Cork, Ireland m.5-37-32
Cornhill (district of London?) m.5-39-46
Cornwallis, Charles, 1st Marquis & 2nd Earl, 1738-1805, General m.1-6-7; 2-15-3; 4-26-32; 5-37-13
Cornwallis, Sir William, 1744-1819, Admiral m.4-26-37
Cossens, Luke (Cozens on Army List) Q.M., officer of 16th Lt. Dragoons 1-5-(41-45)
Coulson, William, Q.M. 16th Lt. Dragoons 1-5-46.
Mentioned: 5-39-48
Cousins, 1-5-47
Coutts, m.1-4-22, 23
Cowden, William 1-5-(48-51)
Cowpox m.5-37-41
Craig, M., cmdr. E. India Co. ship Queen 1-5-(52-54)
[Craufard, Sir Charles Gregan, 1761-1821] Deputy Adj. General 1-5-55, 56
Craven, Lady Elizabeth, d. 1828, wife of Wm., 6th Baron Craven m.5-33-3
Crawford, E. 1-5-57, 58
Crode, Sarah 1-5-59
Crowder, Thomas, Lt. 6th Dragoons 1-5-60
Crozier, George 1-5-61, 62
Cumberland, Prince William Augustus, Duke, of 1721-1765 m.3-19-31
Curacao, West Indies m.2-15-3
Dacke, Berlin 1788 2-9-1
Dana, Francis, soldier m.2-9-2
Dana, James, father of Francis 2-9-2 (c.)
Dashwood, Sir John, 4th Bart., d.1849 m.6-40-16
Dauphin of France SEE Louis Charles de France
Davenport, Henry William, Cornet, 16th Lt. Dragoons m.1-3-60
Davis, soldier? m.3-20-25
Davis, surveyor m.4-30-3, 5
Davis, Ann m.1-1-26
Davis, J. 2-9-(3-5).
Mentioned: 5-34-11
Dax, [F.?] 2-9-6
Deane, Thomas, tradesman 2-9-7
Death of Major Pierson (painting) m.2-13-25
DeCorbiniere, or Decorbiniere, m.3-20-12, 13; 5-34-1
DeGruchy, J. P. m.2-13-44, 45, 50; 4-26-49
Delon, French tutor 2-9-8, 9.
Mentioned: 2-13-27; 3-25-34; 4-26-6, 9b
Denis, m.2-17-10
Depois, Henry, tailor 2-9-(10-13)
Derby, Edward Stanley, 12th Earl of, 1752-1834 m.2-15-7, 8
Dering, Cholmeley, 1766-1836, Col. New Romney Fencibles 2-10-(1-8).
Mentioned: 5-37-6
Dering, Deborah Winchester, Lady, d.1818, wife of Edw., 4th Bart. m.5-37-6
Dering, Sir Edward [6th Bart., d.1798] m.2-10-(3-5)
Desincour, Elizabeth (Zinette), French mistress of Wm. Lee IV 1-4-64; 2-10-(9-33).
Mentioned: 1-3-27, 51; 1-4-(57-75); 2-9-32; 2-12-16; 3-20-12; 3-22-(23-25); [4-28-49]; 5-34-4, 33b.
[Devenish], Thos. C. 2-9-14
Dewar, H. 2-9-15, 16
Dewbery, John 2-9-(17-20)
Dickens, sergeant m.6-42-3
Dickson, Col. H. 2-9-21.
Mentioned: 6-41-(5-9)
Directory (French Gov't.) m.5-39-39
Dissenters m.3-19-16
Don, Sir George, 1754-1832, General 2-9-(22-27)
Donnelly, Peter, tradesman 2-9-(28-30).
Mentioned: 5-34-6; [5-39-6]
Dougé, Mme., French woman, London, 1790 2-9-(31-33)
Douthwaite, Quarter Master m.1-3-56
Down, James 2-9-34
Dragoons SEE ALSO: Regiments by number m.6-42-29
Drainage m.2-13-36
Drew, m.4-31-39
Drury, James, 1750-1834, headmaster of Harrow 2-9-35
Dublin, Ireland m.3-18-13
Dudley, m. 3-23-30
Dudley, B. 2-9-36
Dudley, Samuel m. 1-1-36
Duffin, Thomas 2-9-37.
Mentioned: 3-18-3; 6-40-17
Dumfrieshire, Scotland m.3-24-20
Dumouriez, Charles Francois, 1739-1823, French general m.5-39-25
Duncan, Gideon, ass't. commissary, Ostend 2-9-38
Dundas, Sir David, 1735-1820, General 2-9-39,40.
Mentioned: 1-3-22; 1-6-8; 2-8-7; 2-9-(24-26); 2-17-7; 4-27-42; 4-31-21; 5-39-29
Dungannon, soldier 2-9-41,42.
Mentioned: 3-18-6
Dunn, Francis m.2-9-43; 4-27-(46-57); 5-38-19, 22; 5-39-(34-36); 6-40-30
Dunn, James, father of Francis 2-9-43 (c.)
Durville, Marie de m.5-37-3
Dyke, - courtmartial m.4-31-37; 5-33-2a; 5-34-31
Dyke, Sir John Dixon, 3rd Bart., d. 1810 m.2-13-31
East, Sir Edward Hyde, 1764-1847, chief justice, Calcutta 2-11-1,2.
Mentioned: 5-37-25
East Indies m.5-37-33
Edgeware Estate m.2-13-41; 4-26-48
Edinburgh, Scotland m.5-37-39
Education - England, 18th century m.3-25-25, 29; 4-26-6, 9b
Edward, Prince (later Duke of Kent) 1767-1820, father of Victoria m.1-5-23; 2-15-15; 4-31-33
Edwards, James, horse dealer 2-11-3
11th Light Dragoons m.2-9-27
Elbe River m.1-1-35
Electress m.1-1-33
Eliza m.6-43-5
Elte (place) m.2-12-9
Emerson, James, officer 16th Lt. Dragoons m.5-37-29
Emery, - death m.5-35-11
Emery, Josiah, creditor 2-11-4
Emigrant, (Emigré) cavalry m.4-27-37
Emigrant (Emigré) Corps SEE ALSO: Regiment names m.5-39-32
Emigrants (Emigrés) m.5-37-32
Emmott, Chris 2-11-6, 7.
Mentioned: 1-5-36; 5-36-18
[Ende, G. D.] 2-11-8
Epsom, England m.1-4-5; 3-20-1; 4-31-39
Erkel, Fred, Brunswick waiter 2-11-9
Erroll, George Hay, 15th Earl of, d.1798 m.2-10-2
Erskine, Sir William, 1769-1813, General, 15th Lt. Dragoons m.5-37-13
Evans, 2-11-10, 11
Evelyn, General m.5-32-11
Farm equipment m.5-39-19, 20
Fashions m.2-13-21
Faunce, Edmund, ensign, 4th Regt. Foot 2-12-1 2a
Fawcett, Sir William, 1728-1804, General 2-13-(1-12)
Featherstone, Sir Harry m.2-15-10
Feilding, William Robert Basil, Viscount, 1760-1799, General m. 5-37-30, 32
Fernandez, S., lawyer or banker 2-13-(13-20)
Field, John, deserter m.4-31-26
Fielding SEE Feilding
15th Light Dragoons m.1-3-9; 2-9-25, 26; 5-32-7a
Fiott, Capt., sea captain m.2-13-28
Fiott, John, in-law of Lees
Mentioned: 3-23-18; 4-26-49, 51; 4-28-55; 5-34-14, 33a, 35; 6-40-28
Fiott, John [Jr.?],?son of John 2-13-53, 54, [55]
Fiott, Mrs. John m.3-23-8; 4-26-23, 24
Fish m.4-28-39
Fitzherbert, Maria Anne, 1756-1837, wife of George, Prince of Wales (IV) m.3-18-27
Fitzroy, Frances Mundy, Lady Charles, d.1797 m.3-23-21
Fleuret, Strasbourg creditor 2-12-26
Fonblanque, John de Grenier, 1760-1837, jurist m. 5-36-14
Ford, Joseph, servant 2-12-(3-6).
Mentioned: 1-5-43; 4-31-16; 5-35-22; 5-39-14
Ford, Mary Anson, Lady Francis(1st Bart.) m.4-26-38
Foster, R., soldier 2-12-7.
Mentioned: 5-39-63
Foster, Robert, armourer 2-12-8
Fotheringham, John, mate, Snow Jason 1-1-2
Fox, Charles James, (1749-1806), State of the Union m.2-13-36
Fox, Henry Edward, 1755-1811, military commander 2-12-(9-12); 4-29-1,2
Mentioned: 2-12-1; 6-42-45
Foxall, m.3-24-13
Foxall, John 2-12-13
Fox hunting m.3-18-10; 5-39-3
Fozard, J., friend and agent 2-13-(56-66)
France m.1-4-12; 2-10-3; 3-19-24; 3-24-34; 4-26-14
Franck, P.J., Strasbourg agent 2-12-14,15.
Mentioned: 5-35-4,42
Frankfort, Germany m.2-9-22
Fraser, John G., soldier 2-12-16.
Mentioned: 2-9-8
Frederick, Prince [1750-1765, brother of George III] m.3-19-18
[Frederick Augustus], Prince SEE York, Duke of
Frederick William II, King of Prussia, 1744-1797 m.5-34-20
Freemasons m.5-39-11, 12
French Army m.1-7-19; 2-9-22; 2-15-3; 3-20-19, 21; 5-37-12
Fribourg, P., merchant 2-12-17
Fribourg & Freyer, merchants 2-12-18
Fry, William Jones, officer 16th Lt. Dragoons 2-12-19,20.
Mentioned: 5-37-29,31
G--, Stephen 2-14-1
Garden, J. 2-15-1
Gardner, Henry Farington (or Farrington) d.1792, Col. 16th & 20th Lt. Dr. 1-15-(2-15).
Mentioned: 1-5-50; 1-6-3; 4-31-40; 5-39-2, 9, 12, 63
Gedelier, 2-14-2
George III, King of England, etc., 1738-1820 m.1-2-15, 42, 45; 1-3-48, 62; 2-8-3; 2-17-7; 3-19-4, 10; 3-22-35; 3-23-19, 23; 3-24-8; 4-26-13, 41; 4-28-56; 5-35-33; 5-38-4; 5-39-53; 6-42-44; 6-43-5.
George IV, King of England SEE Wales, Prince of
Gerard, M.P.? m.3-19-20
Gibson, m.1-5-46
Gibson, Robert, saddler 2-14-(3-6)
Gibson Son & Peat, saddler 2-14-7, 8
Gilbert, John, horse dealer? 2-14-9, 10
Gilchrist, [F.?] banker? 2-14-11
Gillespie, Robert, officer 20th Lt. Dragoons m.3-20-29
Gipsy (horse) m.6-42-8
Gloucester, Bishop of (1764) m.3-19-4
Gloucester, Maria, Duchess of, d.1807 m. 6-40-5
Gloucester, William Henry, Duke of, 1743-1805, brother of Geo. III m.6-40-5
Goddard, Samuel, officer 16th Lt. Dragoons 2-14-12.
Mentioned: 1-2-64; 1-4-39, 48
Golding, Edward, soldier 2-14-13
Goodwin, J. 1-5-33
Goodwin, John, corporal, 16th Lt. Dragoons 2-14-14.
[Mentioned: 1-5-46]
[Goparre], 2-14-15
Gordon, m.5-34-4, 17, 25
Gore, m.3-18-16, 26
Goslings & Sharpe 2-14-(16-18)
Gould, Ed., horse dealer? 2-14-19
Grace, Thomas 2-14-20
[Granby Colcroft,?] m.1-3-65
Grand Junction Canal m.2-13-34; 2-14-28
Grand Maison, Mme., French woman 2-14-(21-25).
Mentioned: 1-5-58
Grant, W[illiam Kerr, 1772-1852, General] 2-14-26,27
Grasse, M. de m.4-28-49
Gray, E.O. 2-14-28, 29
Greek the m.1-4-47, 48
Green, John SEE Lincoln, Bishop of woman?
Green, F. N. 2-14-30
Greening, -- Robert 2-14-31
Greenwollers, William, creditor 2-14-32, 33.
Mentioned: 4-28-30
Greenwood, Charles, soldier 2-14-34
Gregory, John, creditor 2-14-35
Grellier, James, veterinary surgeon, 25th Lt. Dragoons 2-14-36, 37.
Mentioned: 4-28-42
Grenier, hotelkeeper 2-14-38, 39
Grenville, George, 1712-1770, statesman m. 3-19-2, 7, 17, 18, 19, 21, 32, 33.
Grenville, Mrs. George m. 3-19-30
Grenville, George Nugent-Temple, 1st Marquis of Buckingham and 2nd Earl Temple, 1753-1813, statesman m. [1-3-1]; 1-4-10; 1-5-17; 3-18-22; 3-19-21; 3-23-20
Grenville, William Wyndham, Baron Grenville, 1759-1834, statesman m. 2-13-38, 41; 3-23-20
Greyhounds m. 1-6-3; 2-17-1; 5-37-9
Griffin, Sir John (orig. Whitwell) 1719-1797, field marshall m. 3-25-20; 4-26-60
Griggs, J., school friend 2-14-40
Grosvener, Richard, 1st Earl, 1731-1802, horse breeder m. 5-34-6
Gudgeon, m. 5-39-43, 44
Guernsey, Isle of m. 2-13-22
Gullier, J., friend 2-14-41, 42
Gwyn, Francis Edward, Major Gen., Col., 25th Lt. Dragoons 1-3-54; 2-14-43.
Mentioned: 2-13-7, 11; 4-26-42; 5-39-44
Hall, T. 2-16-1, 2
Hamburger (town) m. 5-33-1
Hamilton, H.D., Major, 28th Lt. Dragoons 2-16-3
Hammersley,?banker m. 1-4-16
Handel, George Frederick, 1685-1759 m. 3-25-25
[Hannam, I Desincour's lawyer m. 1-4-(57-60), 66,72; 4-28-49
Hannoverians m. 4-27-31
Harcourt, 3-19-36, 37
Harcourt, C. de m. 5-39-32
Harcourt, Chevalier d' m. 4-27-37
Harcourt, Count m. 2-9-37; 4-28-57
Harcourt, Amédée Marie Francois (later marquis) d.1831, British soldier 3-18-3.
Mentioned: 3-23-18
Harcourt, Anne Francois, marquis de and duc de Beuvron, 1727-1797, French general. SEE ALSO: BEUVRON m. 3-19-10
Harcourt, Lady Elizabeth Venables (wife of George Simon), previously Lady Nuneham 5-32-22.
Mentioned: 1-5-48; 3-23-8, 19, 21; 3-25-7; 4-26-34; 5-32-20
Harcourt, Francois Henri, 5th duc (Duke) de, 1726-1802, General 3-18-1, 2.
Mentioned: 3-23-21
Harcourt, George Simon, Lord Nuneham and 2nd Earl Harcourt 1736-1809 5-32-(9-21).
Mentioned: 1-4-13; 1-5-48; 3-18-13, 37; 3-19-7, 11, 18; 3-23-2, 19, 21, 23; 3-25-7; 4-26-34; 5-34-10
Harcourt, Henry, soldier, cousin 3-18-(4-34).
Mentioned: 1-4-70; 1-5-43; [2-9-41]; 2-15-2; 2-17-1; 4-28-53; 5-34-14, 15, 16, 33a; 5-37-9; 5-39-[19]; 6-44-12
Harcourt, Mary Danby Lockhart (wife of William) 3-18-(34-37).
Mentioned: 2-8-36; 3-23-10, 15, 18; 4-28-57; 5-39-28
Harcourt, Simon, 1st Earl Harcourt, 1714-1777 3-19-(1-34).
Mentioned: 3-25-7; 5-32-10, 13, 15, 16.
Harcourt, William, 3rd Earl Harcourt, 1743-1830, field marshall [3-19-35]; 3-23-25; 3-24-18; 4-28-38; 4-30-3, 5, 6, 8, 9.
Mentioned: 1-2-4, 48, 50; 1-3-20, 46; 1-4-24, 25a, 31, 40; 1-7-19, 25; 2-8-3, 36; 2-12-10, 11; 2-15-9; 3-18-23, 35; 3-19-1, 16, 26, 30; 3-20-19, 27, 28; 3-22-16; 3-23-1, [7], 11, 13, 15, 19; 3-24-3; 3-25-9; 4-26-36, 37; 4-27-29; 4-28-32, 57; 4-30-2; 5-32-7b, 10; 5-34-7, 10; 5-36-1, 11, 15; 5-37-34; 5-39-10, 14, 15, [19], 28; 5-39-39, [51], 52, [58]; 6-40-31; 6-42-3; 6-44-7
Harcourt family m. 3-23-2, 18, 23; 4-26-19, 35
Harding, Richard,?East India Co. 2-16-(4-6)
Harper SEE Lees-Harper affair
Harrington, Charles Stanhope, 4th Earl, 1753-1829, General m. 1-4-40
Harrington, J. R.,?insurance broker 2-16-7, 8
Harrington, James, War Office 2-16-(9-11)
Harris, William, jeweler 2-16-12
Harrison, James, veterinary surgeon 16th Lt. Dragoons 2-16-13, 14
Harrow (English school) m. 1-1-14, 15; 2-14-40; 3-25-7, 46; 4-27-1; 5-35-18
Hart, Miss -- m. 4-31-39
Hartwell (estate near Aylesbury) m. 3-19-1, 5; 3-23-1, 29; 4-26-14; 4-28-34, 40, 53; 4-31-15, 16; 5-32-18, [19]; 5-36-14, 22, 23; 5-37-[53]; 5-39-19; 6-43-10
Hartwell (ship) m. 2-13-28
Hawker, Samuel, officer 16th Lt. Dragoons 2-17-(1-11).
Mentioned: 1-7-19; 2-10-2; 5-34-17; 5-38-1
Heathcote, Thomas 2-16-15, 16
Henley, England m. 3-19-5
Herbert, Lord -- m. 5-39-27
Herbert, Hemdorf, police chief of Oldenburg 2-16-17
Hermitage (estate on Continent) m.4-28-57
Herries, Robert 2-16-18
Hewett, Sir George, 1750-1840, General m.2-14-42
Hewitt, [J.], East India Co. cap't. 2-16-19, 20